# **Michael Brickley**

Bloomfield, CT

michael.bricklev1@gmail.com • (860)-989-0800 • www.michaelbricklev.com

#### PERFORMANCE PROFILE

Current data integration analyst with over five years of experience capturing, validating, and analyzing data. Efficiently queries data via SQL and automates tasks via Python. Maintains excellent time-management, completing tasks accurately and promptly. Recently completed advanced degree in software development.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Data Integration Analyst**

May 2020 - Present

Pratt & Whitney, Inc.; East Hartford, CT

- Support F-35 ALIS system via electronic equipment logbook (EEL) validation and delivery
- Troubleshoot and resolve EEL related issues in ALIS via Action Requests
- Develop object oriented Python applications to automate and streamline EEL validation processes
- Utilize Git/GitHub for version control tracking of projects source code
- Point person for resolution of data issues between EEL and provisioning teams'

# **Provisioning Team Lead**

March 2019 - May 2020

Pratt & Whitney, Inc.; East Hartford, CT

- Managed small team (3), delegating tasks and providing guidance accordingly
- Held weekly training sessions to guide and collaborate with team members
- Maintained metrics of department tasks and processes
- Overseer of reconciliation of data into provisioning database

# **Provisioning Data Analyst**

June 2016 – March 2019

Pratt & Whitney, Inc.; East Hartford, CT

- Developed Python application utilizing Agile methodology, to streamline provisioning data process flow
- Supported F-35 ALIS system via provisioning deliverables, to ensure up to date logistics data
- Created/maintained Microsoft Access databases to cleanse and validate data
- Developed Oracle SQL scripts for extraction and analysis of data
- Processed engineering changes to maintain up-to-date F135 bill of material

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Master of Science in Software Development**

May 2020

Boston University; Boston, MA

GPA: 3.5

# **Bachelor of Science in Business Management, Minor in Mathematics**

May 2013

Fairfield University; Fairfield, CT

## **CERTIFICATIONS & SKILLS**

#### **Certifications**:

- Microsoft Office Specialist (Expert) Excel
- Microsoft Office Specialist Access

# Skills:

Python (High), HTML (High), XML (High), SQL (Medium-High), Visio (Medium), Git/GitHub (Medium), Java (Medium), Qlik (Medium-Low), SharePoint (Low)